Guide to the Rice University Art Gallery records, 1971-2017 UA 066
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series IV: Exhibition print materials and curatorial files, 1995-2010
  - James Cullinane, Pastor Collux, 8 June-8 Sept., 2001
    - Correspondence-artist (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Financial (Box 33, Folder 8, Folder 9)
    - Graphics (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Installation (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Photographic (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Post-exhibition (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Press (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Research-articles (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Research-Artist's statement CV (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Travel (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Events, 2000-2001
    - Installation USA/Michael Olijnyk (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Installation USA/Renny Pritikin (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Tom Crow (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - Tom Crow-patron dinner (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - Installation USA/Mary T. Jacob (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Jennifer Steinkamp and Jimmy Johnson, One Saw; the Other Saw, 21 Sept.-28 Oct., 2001
    - Catalog (Box 33, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence (Box 33, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence-artist (Box 33, Folder 24)
    - Financial (Box 33, Folder 25)
    - Graphics (Box 33, Folder 26)
    - Installation (Box 33, Folder 27)
    - Photographic (Box 33, Folder 28)
    - Post-exhibition (Box 33, Folder 29)
    - Press (Box 33, Folder 30)
    - Research-articles (Box 33, Folder 31)
    - Research-artist's statement (Box 33, Folder 32)
  - Liga Pang, Ikasu, 9 Nov.-9 Dec., 2001
    - Catalog (Box 33, Folder 33)
    - Correspondence (Box 33, Folder 34)
    - Correspondence-artist (Box 33, Folder 35)
    - Events (Box 33, Folder 36)
    - Financial (Box 33, Folder 37)
    - Graphics (Box 33, Folder 38)
    - Installation (Box 33, Folder 39)
    - Photographic (Box 33, Folder 40)
    - Press (Box 33, Folder 41)
    - Research-articles (Box 33, Folder 42)
    - Research-previous exhibits (Box 33, Folder 43)
    - Shipping (Box 33, Folder 44)
    - Travel (Box 33, Folder 45)
  - Lee Mingwei, The Tourist Project, 17 Jan.-24 Feb. 2002
    - Catalog (Box 33, Folder 46)
    - Correspondence (Box 33, Folder 47)
    - Correspondence-artist (Box 33, Folder 48)
    - Financial (Box 33, Folder 49)
    - Graphics (Box 33, Folder 50)
    - Installation (Box 33, Folder 51)
    - Photographic (Box 33, Folder 52)
    - Post-exhibition (Box 33, Folder 53)
    - Press kits (Box 33, Folder 54)
    - Press (Box 33, Folder 55)
    - Research (Box 33, Folder 56)
    - Research-CV (Box 33, Folder 57)
    - Research-Houston (Box 33, Folder 58)
    - Tour (Box 33, Folder 59)
  - Adrian Arenas Ilian, the Precious Stone and Gold Factory, 8 March-14 April, 2002
    - Catalog (Box 33, Folder 60)
    - Correspondence (Box 33, Folder 61)
    - Correspondence-artist (Box 33, Folder 62)
    - Events (Box 33, Folder 63)
    - Financial (Box 33, Folder 64)
    - Graphics (Box 33, Folder 65)
    - Installation (Box 33, Folder 66)
    - Photographic (Box 33, Folder 67)
    - Press (Box 33, Folder 68)
    - Research-articles (Box 33, Folder 69)
    - Research-artist's statement CV (Box 33, Folder 70)
    - Research-previous exhibits (Box 33, Folder 71)
  - All That, Student Art Exhibition, 26 April-11 May, 2002 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - David Chien, GustyWindsMayExist, 17 June-1 Sept., 2002
    - Financial (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Graphics (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Installation (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Press (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Ester Partegas, Samesation, 20 Sept.-27 Oct., 2002
    - Catalog (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence-artist (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Financial (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Graphics (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Installation (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Photographic (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Post-exhibition (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Press (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Research-articles (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Research-artist's statement CV (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Shigeru Ban, Bamboo Roof, 9 Nov., 2002-11 May 2003
    - ARUP (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Catalog (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - Collaboration-Harvard (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - Collaboration-Rice School of Architecture (Box 34, Folder 21)
    - Collaboration-University of Houston (Box 34, Folder 22)
    - Copyrights (Box 34, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence (Box 34, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence-artist (Box 34, Folder 25)
    - Events-opening party (Box 34, Folder 26)
    - Events-lecture (Box 34, Folder 27)
    - Financial (Box 34, Folder 28)
    - Graphics (Box 34, Folder 29)
    - Installation (Box 34, Folder 30)
    - Post-exhibition (Box 34, Folder 31)
    - Press (Box 34, Folder 32)
    - Research-articles (Box 34, Folder 33)
    - Research-artist's statement CV (Box 34, Folder 34)
    - Research-previous exhibits (Box 34, Folder 35)
  - Phoebe Washburn, True, False, and Slightly Better, 23 Jan.-23 March, 2003
    - Catalog (Box 34, Folder 36)
    - Correspondence (Box 34, Folder 37)
    - Events (Box 34, Folder 38)
    - Financial (Box 34, Folder 39)
    - Graphics (Box 34, Folder 40)
    - Installation (Box 34, Folder 41)
    - Photographic (Box 34, Folder 42, Folder 43)
    - Press (Box 34, Folder 44)
    - Research-articles (Box 34, Folder 45)
    - Research-artist's statement CV (Box 34, Folder 46)
    - Research-previous exhibits (Box 34, Folder 47)
  - Exit, Student Art Exhibition, 24 April-10 May
    - Correspondence-curator (Box 34, Folder 48)
    - Correspondence-student (Box 34, Folder 49)
    - Curator (Box 34, Folder 50)
    - Graphics (Box 34, Folder 51)
    - Installation (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Press (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Jesse Bercowetz Matt Bua, The Re-creation of Fort Discomfort, 18 Sept.-26 Oct. 2003
    - Catalog (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Events (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Financial (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Graphics (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Installation (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Photographic (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Post-exhibition (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Press (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Research-articles (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Research-artist's statement CV (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Research-previous exhibits (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Tara Donovan, Haze, 6 Nov.-14 Dec. 2003
    - Catalog (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - Financial (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - Graphics (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - Post-exhibition (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - Press (Box 35, Folder 20)
    - Research-articles (Box 35, Folder 21)
    - Research-artist's statement CV (Box 35, Folder 22)
    - Research-previous exhibits (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - Heather Ackroyd Dan Harvey, Green brick, Green back, 22 Jan.-4 April 2004
    - Catalog (Box 35, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence (Box 35, Folder 25)
    - Financial (Box 35, Folder 26)
    - Graphics (Box 35, Folder 27)
    - Installation (Box 35, Folder 28)
    - Photographic (Box 35, Folder 29)
    - Post-exhibition (Box 35, Folder 30)
    - Events (Box 35, Folder 31)
    - Press (Box 35, Folder 32)
    - Research-articles (Box 35, Folder 33)
    - Research-artist's statement CV (Box 35, Folder 34)
    - Research-previous exhibits (Box 35, Folder 35)
    - Research-previous lectures (Box 35, Folder 36)
    - Site visit (Box 35, Folder 37)
  - Under the Radar, Student Art Exhibition, 22 April-8 May 2004
    - Correspondence (Box 35, Folder 38)
    - Graphics (Box 35, Folder 39)
    - Installation (Box 35, Folder 40)
    - Press (Box 35, Folder 41)
  - Alyson Shotz, the Shape of Space, 1 June-27 Aug. 2004
    - Correspondence (Box 35, Folder 42)
    - Financial (Box 35, Folder 43)
    - Graphics (Box 35, Folder 44)
    - Installation (Bin 35, Folder 45)
    - Photographic (Box 35, Folder 46)
    - Post-exhibition (Box 35, Folder 47)
    - Press (Box 35, Folder 48)
    - Research-articles (Box 35, Folder 49)
    - Research-artist's statement CV (Box 35, Folder 50)
    - Research-previous exhibits (Box 35, Folder 51)
  - Jessica Stockholder, Sam Ran Over Sand or Sand Ran Over Sam, 16 Sept.-31 Oct. 2004
    - Catalog (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Collaboration (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Design (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Events (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Financial (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Graphics (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Installation (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Photographic (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Post-exhibition (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Press (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Resesarch-articles (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Research-artist's statement CV (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - Research-previous exhibits (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - Research-transcripts (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - Video (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Allen Ruppersberg, the Singing Posters, 11 Nov.-12 Dec. 2004
    - Catalog (Box 36, Episode 17)
    - Correspondence (Box 36, Folder 18)
    - Events (Box 36, Folder 19)
    - Financial (Box 36, Folder 20)
    - Graphics (Box 36, Folder 21)
    - Installation (Box 36, Folder 22)
    - Photographic (Box 36, Folder 23)
    - Post-exhibition (Box 36, Folder 24)
    - Press (Box 36, Folder 25)
    - Research-articles (Box 36, Folder 26)
    - Research-artist's statement (Box 36, Folder 27)
    - Research-transcripts (Box 36, Folder 28)
  - Eve Sussman, 89 seconds at Alcazar, 20 Jan-27 FEb. 2005
    - Article (Box 36, Folder 29)
    - Artist (Box 36, Folder 30)
    - Credits (Box 36, Folder 31)
    - Design (Box 36, Folder 32)
    - Foreward (Box 36, Folder 33)
    - Images (Box 36, Folder 34)
    - Interview (Box 36, Folder 35)
  - Jacob Hashimoto, Superabundant Atmosphere, 17 March-17 April 2005
    - Catalog (Box 36, Folder 36)
    - Correspondence (Box 36, Folder 37)
    - Events (Box 36, Folder 38)
    - Financial (Box 36, Folder 39)
    - Graphics (Box 36, Folder 40)
    - Installation (Box 36, Folder 41)
    - Photographic (Box 36, Folder 42)
    - Post-exhibition (Box 36, Folder 43)
    - Press (Box 36, Folder 44)
    - Research-articles (Box 36, Folder 45)
    - Research-artist's statement (Box 36, Folder 46)
    - Research-previous exhibits (Box 36, Folder 47)
    - Research-transcripts (Box 36, Folder 48)
  - Output, Student Art Exhibition, 28 April-14 May 2005
    - Correspondence (Box 36, Folder 49)
    - Financial (Box 36, Folder 50)
    - Graphics (Box 36, Folder 51)
    - Installation (Box 36, Folder 52)
    - Photographic (Box 36, Folder 51)
    - Press (Box 36, Folder 54)
    - Research-curator (Box 36, Folder 55)
  - Jessica Stockholder (Press), 2005 (Box 36, Folder 57)
  - Diane Landry, Flying School and Mandala Naya, 33 Sept.-30 Oct. 2005
    - Catalog (Box 36, Folder 56)
    - Correspondence (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Events (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Financial (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Graphics (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Installation (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Photographic (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Post-exhibition (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Press (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Research-articles (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Research-artist's statement (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Research-previous exhibits (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Research-transcripts (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Video (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - White Webb, Eminent Domain, 10 Nov.-11 Dec. 2005
    - Correspondence (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Events (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - Financial (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - Graphics (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - Installation (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - Post-exhibition (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - Press (Box 37, Folder 20)
    - Research-articles (Box 37, Folder 21)
    - Research-artist's statement (Box 37, Folder 22)
    - Research-transcripts (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - David Ellis, Conversation, 19 Jan.-5 March 2006
    - Catalog (Box 37, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence (Box 37, Folder 25)
    - Events (Box 37, Folder 26)
    - Financial (Box 37, Folder 27)
    - Graphics (Box 37, Folder 28)
    - Installation (Box 37, Folder 29)
    - Post-exhibition (Box 37, Folder 30)
    - Press (Box 37, Folder 31)
    - Research-articles (Box 37, Folder 32)
    - Research-artist's statement CV (Box 37, Folder 33)
    - Research-previous exhibits (Box 37, Folder 34)
    - Research-transcripts (Box 37, Folder 35)
  - Shine, Student Art Exhibition, 27 April-13 May 2006
    - Correspondence (Box 37, Folder 36)
    - Financial (Box 37, Folder 37)
    - Graphics (Folder 37, Folder 38)
    - Photographic (Box 37, Folder 39)
    - Press (Box 37, Folder 40)
    - Research-artist's statement CV (Box 37, Folder 41)
  - Lisa Hoke, Light My Fire, 19 May-31 Aug. 2006
    - Correspondence (Box 37, Folder 42)
    - Financial (Box 37, Folder 43)
    - Graphics (Box 37, Folder 44)
    - Installation (Box 37, Folder 45)
    - Post-exhibition (Box 37, Folder 46)
    - Press (Box 37, Folder 47)
    - Research-articles (Box 37, Folder 48)
    - Research-artist's statement CV (Box 37, Folder 49)
    - Research-previous exhibits (Box 37, Folder 50)
    - Video (Box 37, Folder 51)
  - Benjamin Ball Gaston Nogues, Rip Curl Canyon, 21 Sept.-29 Oct. 2006
    - Catalog (Box 37, Folder 52)
    - Correspondence (Box 37, Folder 53)
    - Events (Box 37, Folder 54)
    - Financial (Box 37, Folder 55)
    - Graphics (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Installation (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Press (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Research-articles (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Research-artist's statement, bio, CV (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Research-previous exhibits (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Research-transcripts (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - John Cerney, Big Landscape, Big West, 9 Nov.-10 Dec. 2006
    - Catalog (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Collaboration (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Financial (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Graphics (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Images checklist (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - Installation (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Post-exhibition (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - Press (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - Research-articles (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - Research-previous exhibits (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - Transcripts (Box 38, Folder 19)
    - Travel (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Judy Pfaff, ...all of the above, 1 Feb.-1 April 2007
    - Catalog (Box 38, Folder 21)
    - DVD video (Box 38, Folder 22)
    - Events (Box 38, Folder 23)
    - Financial (Box 38, Folder 24)
    - Graphics (Box 38, Folder 25)
    - Press (Box 38, Folder 26)
    - Research-articles (Box 38, Folder 27)
    - Research-artist's statement, bio, CV (Box 38, Folder 28)
    - Research-previous exhibits (Box 38, Folder 29)
    - Reseach-transcripts (Box 38, Folder 30)
  - Art for Profit, Student Art Exhibition, 26 April-13 May 2007
    - Artist's statement, bio, CV (Box 38, Folder 31)
    - Financial (Box 38, Folder 32)
    - Graphics (Box 38, Folder 33)
    - Press (Box 38, Folder 34)
  - Mike Stilkey, When the Animals Rebel, 4 June-31 Aug. 2007
    - Correspondence (Box 38, Folder 35)
    - Events (Box 38, Folder 36)
    - Financial (Box 38, Folder 37)
    - Graphics (Box 38, Folder 38)
    - Installation (Box 38, Folder 39)
    - Press (Box 38, Folder 40)
    - Research-articles (Box 38, Folder 41)
    - Research-previous exhibits (Box 38, Folder 42)
    - Transcripts (Box 38, Folder 43)
    - Travel (Box 38, Folder 44)
  - Kirsten Hassenfeld, Dans la Lune, 27 Sept.-9 Dec. 2007
    - Catalog (Box 38, Folder 45)
    - Correspondence (Box 38, Folder 46)
    - Financial (Box 38, Folder 47)
    - Graphics (Box 38, Folder 48)
    - Installation (Box 38, Folder 49)
    - Photographic (Box 38, Folder 50)
    - Post-exhibition (Box 38, Folder 51)
    - Press (Box 38, Folder 52)
    - Transcripts (Box 38, Folder 53)
  - Charlie Roberts, Mambo Jambo: Cabinet of the Cosmos, 24 Jan.-2 March 2008
    - Catalog (Box 38, Folder 54)
    - Correspondence (Box 38, Folder 55)
    - Events (Box 38, Folder 56)
    - Financial (Box 38, Folder 57)
    - Graphics (Box 38, Folder 58)
    - Installation (Box 38, Folder 59)
    - Press (Box 38, Folder 60)
    - Research-transcripts (Box 38, Folder 61)
    - Travel (Box 38, Folder 62)
  - Launch: Student Art Exhibition, 24 April-10 May 2008
    - Correspondence (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Events (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Financial (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Graphics (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Press (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Mark Fox, Dust, 29 May-29 Aug. 2008
    - Correspondence (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - DVD video (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Financial (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Graphics (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Press (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Research (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Travel (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Aurora Robson, The Great Indoors, 18 Sept.-26 Oct. 2008
    - Catalog (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - DVD video (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - Events (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - Financial (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - Graphics (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - Installation (Box 39, Folder 19)
    - Photographic (Box 39, Folder 20)
    - Press (Box 39, Folder 21)
    - Research (Box 39, Folder 22)
    - Reseach-transcripts (Box 39, Folder 23)
    - Travel (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - Michael Salter, Too Much, 6 Nov.-14 Dec. 2008
    - Catalog (Box 39, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence (Box 39, Folder 26)
    - DVD video (Box 39, Folder 27)
    - Financial (Box 39, Folder 28)
    - Graphics (Box 39, Folder 29)
    - Installation (Box 39, Folder 39)
    - Press (Box 39, Folder 31)
    - Research (Box 39, Folder 32)
    - Research-transcripts (Box 39, Folder 33)
    - Travel (Box 39, Folder 34)
  - Paul Villinski, Emergency Response Studio, 29 Jan.-1 March 2009
    - Catalog (Box 39, Folder 35)
    - Correspondence (Box 39, Folder 36)
    - DVD video (Box 39, Folder 37)
    - Events (Box 39, Folder 38)
    - Financial (Box 39, Folder 39)
    - Graphics (Box 39, Folder 40)
    - Post-exhibiton (Box 39, Folder 41)
    - Press (Box 39, Folder 42)
    - Research (Box 39, Folder 43)
    - Travel (Box 39, Folder 44)
  - Henrique Oliveira, Tapumes, 26 March-9 May 2009
    - Catalog (Box 39, Folder 45)
    - Correspondence (Box 39, Folder 46)
    - Events (Box 39, Folder 47)
    - Financial (Box 39, Folder 48)
    - Graphics (Box 39, Folder 49)
    - Installation (Box 39, Folder 50)
    - Press (Box 39, Folder 51)
    - Research (Box 39, Folder 52)
    - Transcripts (Box 39, Folder 53)
    - Travel (Box 39, Folder 54)
  - Wayne White, Big Lectric Fan to Keep Me Cool While I Sleep, 10 Sept.-18 Oct. 2009
    - Catalog (Box 39, Folder 55)
    - Correspondence (Box 39, Folder 56)
    - Events (Box 39, Folder 57)
    - Financial (Box 39, Folder 58)
    - Graphics (Box 39, Folder 59)
    - Installation (Box 39, Folder 60)
    - Photographic (Box 39, Folder 61)
    - Post-exhibition (Box 39, Folder 62)
    - Press (Box 39, Folder 63)
    - Research (Box 39, Folder 64)
    - Travel (Box 39, Folder 65)
  - El Anatsui, Gli, 28 Jan.-14 March 2010
    - Catalog (Box 39, Folder 66)
    - Correspondence (Box 39, Folder 67)
    - DVD video (Box 39, Folder 68)
    - Events (Box 39, Folder 69)
    - Financial (Box 39, Folder 70)
    - Graphics (Box 39, Folder 71)
    - Installation (Box 39, Folder 72)
    - Photographic (Box 39, Folder 73)
    - Post-exhibition (Box 39, Folder 74)
    - Press (Box 39, Folder 75)
    - Research (Box 39, Folder 76)
    - Research-transcripts (Box 39, Folder 77)
    - Travel (Box 39, Folder 78)
- Series V: Exhibition photography (digital), 1995-2012
  General
  Includes the following digital objects stored in nearline system: UA0066aip_001
  - Fall 1994 - Spring 1995 exhibit installations, openings and events
    Scope and Contents
    Exhibits include: Golub Piper; Think Deeply and Well; To the Point 32.
  - Fall 1995 - Spring 1996 exhibit installations, openings and events
    Exhibits include: Cybervato; Day Without Art; Michael Shaughnessy; Narrating the Self 33; Seductive Matter; Y. David Chung.
  - Fall 1996 - Spring 1997 exhibit installations, openings and events
    Exhibits include: Art Matters; Eve Andree Laramee; Fred Tamselli; Sol LeWitt.
  - Fall 1997 - Spring 1998 exhibit installations, openings and events
    Exhibits include: Antonio Martorell; Charles Howard; Collapse; Gary Hill; Yayoi Kusama.
  - Fall 1998 - Spring 1999 exhibit installations, openings and events
    Exhibits include: Jane Miller; Michael Petry; Moving On; Nicole Eisenman; Stepehen Kene.
  - Fall 1999 - Spring 2000 exhibit installations, openings and events
    Exhibits include: Barry McGee; Check It Out; Clubs of Bamako; Shout Outs; Stephen Hendee.
  - Fall 2000 - Spring 2001 exhibit installations, openings and events
    Exhibits include: Celeste Mougenot; James Cullinane; Karim Rashid; Martha Burgess; On the Verge; Winter Horbelt.
  - Fall 2001 - Spring 2002 exhibit installations, openings and events
    Exhibits include: Adriana Arenas Ilian; All That; David Chien; Jennifer Steinkamp; Lee Mingwei; Liga Pang.
  - Fall 2002 - Spring 2003 exhibit installations, openings and events
    Exhibits include: Ester Partegas; Exit; Phoebe Washburn; Shigeru Ban.
  - Fall 2003 - Spring 2004 exhibit installations, openings and events
    Exhibits include: Ackroyd Harvey; Alyson Shotz; Bercowetz Bua; Tara Donovan; Under the Radar.
  - Fall 2004 - Spring 2005 exhibit installations, openings and events
    Exhibits include: Allen Ruppersberg; Eve Sussman; Jacob Hashimoto; Jessica Stockholder; Output.
  - Fall 2005 - Spring 2006 exhibit installations, openings and events
    Exhibits include: David Ellis; Diane Landry; Lisa Hoke; Shine; White Webb.
  - Fall 2006 - Spring 2007 exhibit installations, openings and events
    Exhibits include: Art for Profit; Ball Nogues; John Cerney; Judy Pfaff; Mike Stilkey.
  - Fall 2007 - Spring 2008 exhibit installations, openings and events
    Exhibits include: Charlie Roberts; Kirsten Hassenfeld; Launch; Mark Fox; Miscellaneous.
  - Fall 2008 - Spring 2009 exhibit installations, openings and events
    Exhibits include: Aurora Robson; Henrique Oliveira; Michael Saulter; Miscellaneous; Paul Villinski.
  - Fall 2009 - Spring 2010 exhibit installations, openings and events
    Exhibits include: Andrea Dezso; El Anatsui; Wayne White.
  - Fall 2010 - Spring 2011 exhibit installations, openings and events
    Exhibits include: Mary Temple; Sarah Oppenheimer.
  - Fall 2011 - Spring 2012 exhibit installations, openings, and events
    Exhibits include Ana Serrano, Joel Shapiro, Texas Contemporary, and Yasuaki Onishi
  - Fall 2012 - Spring 2013 exhibit installations, openings, and events, 2012-2013
    Exhibits include Gunilla Klingberg and Soo Sunny Park.
  - Fall 2013 - Spring 2014 exhibit installations, openings, and events, 2013-2014
    Exhibition images include Dinh Q Le, El Ultimo Grito, and Gaia.
  - Fall 2014 - Spring 2015 exhibit installations, openings, and events, 2014-2015
    Exhibitions include Atelier Bow-Wow, Ben Butler, Texas Contemporary Art Fair, and Yusuke Asai.
- Series VI: Exhibition print materials and curatorial files, 2010-2015
  - Sometimes in my Dreams I Fly, Andrea Deszo, April 8 - August 8, 2010: Installation (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Sometimes in my Dreams I Fly, Andrea Deszo, April 8 - August 8, 2010: Correspondence (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Sometimes in my Dreams I Fly, Andrea Deszo, April 8 - August 8, 2010: Press received (Box 40, Folder 3-4)
  - Sometimes in my Dreams I Fly, Andrea Deszo, April 8 - August 8, 2010: Graphics (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - D-17, Sarah Oppenheimer, Sept. 16-Dec. 5, 2010: Installation (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - D-17, Sarah Oppenheimer, Sept. 16-Dec. 5, 2010: graphics (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - D-17, Sarah Oppenheimer, Sept. 16-Dec. 5, 2010: Guestbook (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - D-17, Sarah Oppenheimer, Sept. 16-Dec. 5, 2010: Catalogue (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - D-17, Sarah Oppenheimer, Sept. 16-Dec. 5, 2010: Travel (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - D-17, Sarah Oppenheimer, Sept. 16-Dec. 5, 2010: Correspondence (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - D-17, Sarah Oppenheimer, Sept. 16-Dec. 5, 2010: Research (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - D-17, Sarah Oppenheimer, Sept. 16-Dec. 5, 2010: Research notebook (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - D-17, Sarah Oppenheimer, Sept. 16-Dec. 5, 2010: Photos (Box 41, Folder 9)